export const questionObject = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'Where is the most dangerous place in the machine for a mechanic to work?',
    options: [
      'Between the pit cusion and the ball lift rods',
      'Between the deck and the turret',
      'Under the deck assembly',
      'In the pit conveyor',
    ],
    answer: 'Between the deck and turret',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'When the bowler has delivered the bowling ball, the ball will strike the ___ thereby triggering the pinsetter.',
    options: ['Pins', 'Rake', 'Pin Deck', 'Pit Cushion'],
    answer: 'Pit Cushion',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'There are two large wheels at the rear of the pinsetter that rotate in opposite directions. They are called the ___ and the ___',
    options: [
      'Drive wheel, Pin wheel',
      'Ball Wheel, Magnet wheel',
      'Ball wheel, pin wheel',
      'Front Wheel, Rear Wheel',
    ],
    answer: 'Ball wheel, pin wheel',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'What steps should be followed in order to clear a turn pan jam (TPJ)?',
    options: [
      'Remove power from machine, rotate pin wheel CCW and then remove pins',
      'Remove power from the machine, rotate pin wheel CW and then remove pins.',
      'Remove power from the machine, pry down turn pan and then remove pins.',
      'All of the above.',
    ],
    answer:
      'Remove power from machine, pry down turn pan and then remove pins.',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'Which of the following items will cause the pin wheel to stop turning?',
    options: [
      'Pin gate locked',
      'Turret jammed',
      'Cross conveyor micro switch open',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'All of the above',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'What does the pinsetter do at 270 degrees during a first ball, standing pins cycle?',
    options: [
      'Sets 10 new pins',
      'Respots standing pins',
      'Scissors close',
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'Scissors Close',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'A complete cycle of the pinsetter is considered to be ___ degrees',
    options: ['360', '270', '180', '90'],
    answer: '360',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'The ___ carries the pins across the top of the Pinsetter and places them, one at a time, into the ___',
    options: [
      'Turn pan, Cross Conveyor',
      'Cross Conveyor, Moving Deck',
      'Cross Conveyor, turret',
      'Turret, Moving Deck',
    ],
    answer: 'Cross Conveyor, Turret',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'What is the name of the components on the deck assembly that picks up the standing pins from the lane?',
    options: [
      'Deck pads',
      'Toggle Levers',
      'Scissors',
      'Respot Cells',
      'Fingers',
    ],
    answer: 'Scissors',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'During normal operation, the pinsetter is able to stop at 90 degrees. What condition would require the pinsetter to stop at this position?',
    options: [
      'Blackout',
      'OOR (Out Of Range)',
      'Turn pan jam',
      'Pin gate locked',
    ],
    answer: 'OOR (Out Of Range)',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question: 'What clears the deadwood off of the lane?',
    options: ['Deck', 'Sweep', 'Rake', 'Scissors'],
    answer: 'Rake',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'During normal operation, the pinsetter is able to stop at 180 degrees. What condition would require the pinsetter to stop at this point?',
    options: [
      'Pin gate locked',
      'OOR',
      'Pinsetter waiting for pins to be delivered to the moving deck',
      'Pinsetter has blacked out due to multiple pins in the 5 pin deck chute',
    ],
    answer: 'Pin gate locked',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'During normal operation, the pinsetter is able to stop at 360 degrees. What condition would require the pinsetter to stop at this position?',
    options: ['Blackout', 'OOR', 'Pin gate locked', 'End of the cycle'],
    answer: 'End of the cycle',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'The ___ receives the pins either head first or bottom first, turns them and deposits them all base first on to the ___',
    options: [
      'Turn pan, Cross Conveyor',
      'Pin wheel, Cross Conveyor',
      'Cross Conveyor, Turret',
      'Pit Conveyor, Pin Wheel',
    ],
    answer: 'Turn pan, Cross Conveyor',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    title: 'Blackout',
    question:
      'What is the first thing you should do when a pinsetter shuts itself off electronically by a deck or turret jam?',
    options: [
      "Clear the call quickly so the bowler doesn't have to wait.",
      'Shut the machine off and clear call.',
      'Lockout/Tagout the machine.',
      'Pull the pin out of the deck chutes',
    ],
    answer: 'Lockout / Tagout the machine',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    title: 'Blackout',
    question:
      'What two safety switches will automatically shut off the pinsetter in the event of a pin jam?',
    options: [
      'Deck jam switch, turret jam switch',
      'Deck jam switch, thermal overload',
      'Mechanics safety switch, circuit breaker',
      'Turret jam switch, circuit breaker',
    ],
    answer: 'Deck jam switch, Turret jam switch',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    title: 'Gear Box',
    question: 'What in the gear box drives the 1:1',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', 'Gear box clutch'],
    answer: '2:1',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    title: 'Gear Box',
    question:
      'What in the gear box controls the forward and rearward movement of the moving deck?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '1:1',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    title: 'Gear Box',
    question: 'What in the gear box disengages the gear box clutch?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '4:1',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question: 'What in the gear box drives the 4:1?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: 'Worm shaft',
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question:
      'What in the gear box controls the up and down movement of the deck assembly?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '2:1',
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question: 'What in the gear box drives the detector?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '1:1',
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question:
      'What in the gear box controls the height of the rake throughout the pinsetter cycle?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '1:1',
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question:
      'What in the gear box controls the rearward and forward movement of the rake?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '4:1',
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question:
      'What in the gear box controls the opening and closing of the scissors?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '1:1',
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question: 'What in the gear box drives the 2:1?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '4:1',
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    title: 'Gear box',
    question:
      'What in the gear box controls the height of the clutch reset lever during the pinsetter cycle?',
    options: ['Worm shaft', '4:1', '2:1', '1:1'],
    answer: '1:1',
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    title: 'Maintenance',
    question:
      'Should you forget how to install a belt you can check the following for a reminder',
    options: [
      'An adjacent machine',
      'The service manual',
      'The parts manual',
      'All the above',
    ],
    answer: 'All the above',
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    title: 'Turret',
    question: 'What is the indexing sequence for the turret?',
    options: [
      '5,8,7,4,2,1,3,6,10,9',
      '1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10',
      '9,10,6,3,1,2,4,7,8,5',
      '9,10,6,2,1,3,4,7,8,5',
    ],
    answer: '9,10,6,3,1,2,4,7,8,5',
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    title: 'Turret',
    question:
      'The pin passes over the snubber, falls into the turret basket wire and strikes the ___ causing the turret to index.',
    options: [
      'Indexing trip lever',
      'Indexing pedal',
      'Indexing bell crank',
      'Pin release lever',
    ],
    answer: 'Indexing trip lever',
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question:
      'The pinsetter is powered by an electric motor. What size is the motor?',
    options: [
      '1/2 horsepower',
      '3/4 horsepower',
      '1 horsepower',
      '2 horsepower',
    ],
    answer: '1 horsepower motor',
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    title: 'Deck',
    question: 'The deck holding hook is used for what purpose?',
    options: [
      'To hold the deck from setting new pins.',
      'To keep the deck from lowering to detect pins during a 2nd ball cycle.',
      'To keep the rake from sweeping until it is needed.',
      'To keep the deck from lowering while the rake is sweeping.',
    ],
    answer: 'To keep the deck from lowering while the rake is sweeping',
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    title: 'Pin Gate',
    question: 'The function of the pin gate is to:',
    options: [
      'To stop the pins at the top of the cross conveyor',
      'To control the flow of pins into the turret',
      'To allow pins to go into the turret',
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'To control the flow of pins into the turret',
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    title: 'Pinsetter',
    question: 'The function of the magnetic clutch is to:',
    options: [
      'To turn the pin wheel jackshaft',
      'To turn the pin wheel',
      'To turn the pin wheel drive pulley',
      'To power the turret clutch',
    ],
    answer: 'To turn the pin wheel drive pulley',
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    title: 'Gear Box',
    question: 'The gear box supplies power for the following:',
    options: [
      'Rake and deck',
      'Cross conveyor and turret',
      'Rake and turret',
      'Deck and turret',
    ],
    answer: 'Rake and Deck',
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    title: 'Rake',
    question: 'The rake begins its sweeping motion at what degree?',
    options: ['45 degrees', '90 degrees', '270 degrees', '315 degrees'],
    answer: '90 degrees',
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    title: 'Rake',
    question: 'The rake finishes its sweeping motion at what degree?',
    options: ['180 degrees', '225 degrees', '270 degrees', '315 degrees'],
    answer: '180 degrees',
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    title: 'Maintenance',
    question:
      'What switch on the rear of the wire channel needs to be in the on position in order for the pinsetter to operate?',
    options: [
      'Main circuit breaker',
      'Mechanics safety switch',
      'Thermal overload',
      'Managers control switch',
    ],
    answer: 'Mechanics safety switch',
  },
];
